layitlow.com 2010-06-21

# LayItLow.com Privacy Statement

Information Collection Notice  
Cookies and Tracking Technology  
Information Collected  
Information Sharing and Disclosure  
Review and Delete Your Account and Information  
Data Security  
Children and Privacy  
Forum Guidelines and Rules  
Third Party Sites  
Changes to this Privacy Policy  
Questions or Suggestions

LayItLow.com respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us. Generally, you can browse through our website without giving us any information about yourself. When we do need your personal information to provide services that you request or when you choose to provide us with your personal information, this policy describes how we collect and use your personal information.

##### Information Collection

Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, birth date, gender, occupation, industry, personal interests, other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

When you browse our website, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously indicated that you wish LayItLow.com to remember your login and password. We don't automatically collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our website. Like many other websites, the LayItLow.com website may use a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how you use the site. Please go to "Cookies and Tracking Information" below for more information.

LayItLow.com collects personal information when you use certain LayItLow.com products or services, submit an entry for a sweepstakes or other promotions, or when you submit your personal information to LayItLow.com for any other reason. From time to time, LayItLow.com receives personal information from business partners and vendors. We only use such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws.

##### Notice

When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection. LayItLow.com will not transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled "Information Sharing and Disclosure" below.

If you choose to provide us with your personal information, we may only transfer that information, within LayItLow.com or to LayItLow.com's third party service providers with your permission. Upon receiving your permission, we may transfer your information across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries or jurisdictions around the world.

We will always give you the opportunity to "opt out" of receiving direct marketing or market research information. This means we assume you have given us your consent to collect and use your information in accordance with this Policy unless you take affirmative action to indicate that you do not consent, for instance by clicking or checking the appropriate option or box at the point of collection. In some cases, when applicable, we will provide you with the opportunity to "opt in." This means we will require your affirmative action to indicate your consent before we use your information for purposes other than the purpose for which it was submitted.

##### Cookies and Tracking Technology

A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of LayItLow.com use cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on LayItLow.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of LayItLow.com if you do so. In particular, you may be required to accept cookies in order to complete certain actions on our website. You do not need to have cookies turned on, however, to use/navigate through many parts of our website, except access to some parts of LayItLow.com may require a login and password.

##### How We Use Information Collected

LayItLow.com uses information for several general purposes: to fulfill your requests for certain products and services, to personalize your experience on our website, to keep you up to date on the latest forum announcements, updates, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about either from us or from our business partners, and to better understand your needs and provide you with better services. We may also use your information to send you, or to have our business partners send you, direct marketing information or contact you for market research.

##### Information Sharing and Disclosure

Your personal information is never shared outside LayItLow.com without your permission, except under conditions explained below. Inside LayItLow.com, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access. Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country where LayItLow.com, it's affiliates or agents are located.

LayItLow.com may send your personal information to other entitites or people under any of the following circumstances: when we have your consent to share the information; we need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested; we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of LayItLow.com to provide a product or service to you (we will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose); or we want to keep you up to date on the latest announcements, updates, special offers or other information we think you'd like to hear about either from us or from our business partners. We will also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites.

##### Your Ability to Review and Delete Your Account and Information

If you are a registered forum user, review and edit your profile information by accessing your control panel at [http://www.layitlow.com/forums](http://www.layitlow.com/forums/). You may also request deletion of your LayItLow.com forums account or any of your personal information held by us by sending an email to .

##### Data Security

Your LayItLow.com account information is password-protected for your privacy and security. LayItLow.com safeguards the security of the data you send us with physical, electronic, and managerial procedures. In certain areas of our websites, LayItLow.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

##### Children and Privacy

Our websites do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13. LayItLow.com does not knowingly solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 or send them requests for personal information.

##### Forum Guidelines and Rules

You agree, through your use of this service, that you will not use our forums to post any material which is knowingly false and/or defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, vulgar, hateful, harassing, obscene, profane, sexually oriented, threatening, invasive of a person's privacy, or otherwise violative of any law.

You agree not to post any copyrighted material unless you have permission from the copyright owner or the copyright is owned by you or by LayItLow.com.

LayItLow.com does not assume any legal or financial responsiblity for products, services or other actuals offered through the forums or classifieds. There are risks which you assume when doing business with someone over the Internet. While we recommend that users make appropriate enquiries and take proper precautions before completing transactions, all liability for transactions remain solely with the buyers and sellers. If you cannot agree to these terms for any reason or if the law in your City, County, State or residing area limits or prohibits such activities by you or disclaimers by us - you are not authorized to use the LayItLow.com Forums.

While we prefer an open atmosphere on this site, the forums are not an "anything goes" message board. Please keep in mind the following rules:  

  * No Pornographic images or videos. Please do not post pictures of nudity in the forums.
  * No vulgar, obscene or hateful images (such as extreme pictures of graphic violence, veraciously crude materials, etc.)
  * No hateful speech (racist remarks, overt harassment, etc.) or like attacks against another member, or group of members.
  * No Avatar Abuse. Please keep your avatars fairly clean. No pornography in the avatars.
  * No spamming. Spamming is characterized by the initiation of threads or posts that contribute nothing to a forum. Examples include: empty bodies, bodies with few words that have no relation to the current thread or discussion and those posts that state they are spam, either to annoy or increase a member's post count. This determination is made by the forum Moderator or Administrator and is not up for discussion.
  * Posts in a particular forum need to stay on topic as much as possible. If you want to talk about something that is drastically removed from the topic of a forum, please use the Off Topic forum.

##### Third Party Sites

Our website may contain links to websites operated by other companies. Some of these third-party sites may be co-branded with a LayItLow.com logo, even though they are not operated or maintained by LayItLow.com. Although we choose our business partners carefully, LayItLow.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of web sites operated by third parties that are linked to our site. Once you have left our website, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party website to determine how they will handle any information they collect from you. This also applies to advertising which may be displayed to you, check those [third party websites](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) to view their individual privacy policies and opt-out information.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit [networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

We partner with ValueClick to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. ValueClick may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml](http://www.valueclickmedia.com/member_privacy.shtml).

##### Changes to this Privacy Policy

LayItLow.com will amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site.

##### Questions or Suggestions

If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at .

This document was last updated June 4, 2010
